{
    "questionSet1": [
      { "id": 1, "question": "Solve for x: 2x + 5 = 11", "answer": 3 },
      { "id": 2, "question": "Find the value of y: 3y - 7 = 14", "answer": 7 },
      { "id": 3, "question": "Simplify the expression: 4a + 2b - 3a + b", "answer": "b + 2a" },
      { "id": 4, "question": "Solve the equation: 2(x - 4) = 10", "answer": 9 },
      { "id": 5, "question": "Evaluate the expression for x = 3: 2x^2 - 5x + 1", "answer": 16 },
      { "id": 6, "question": "Solve for y: 5y + 8 = 3y - 2", "answer": -5 },
      { "id": 7, "question": "Simplify the expression: 2(x + 3) - 4", "answer": "2x + 2" },
      { "id": 8, "question": "Solve the equation: 3y = 9", "answer": 3 },
      { "id": 9, "question": "Find the value of a: 2(a - 1) = 10", "answer": 6 },
      { "id": 10, "question": "Evaluate the expression for x = 2: (x + 3)^2", "answer": 25 },
      { "id": 11, "question": "Solve for b: 4b - 7 = 5", "answer": 3 },
      { "id": 12, "question": "Simplify the expression: 3x - 2(x - 5)", "answer": "5 - x" },
      { "id": 13, "question": "Solve the equation: 2y + 6 = 12", "answer": 3 },
      { "id": 14, "question": "Find the value of c: 5c + 2c - 8 = 14", "answer": 2 },
      { "id": 15, "question": "Evaluate the expression for x = -2: -3x^2 + 2x - 1", "answer": -27 }
    ],
    "questionsSet2": [
        { "id": 16, "question": "Solve for x: 3x + 2 = 14", "answer": 4 },
        { "id": 17, "question": "Find the value of y: 2y - 5 = 11", "answer": 8 },
        { "id": 18, "question": "Simplify the expression: 5a + 3b - 2a + 2b", "answer": "3a + 5b" },
        { "id": 19, "question": "Solve the equation: 4(x - 2) = 20", "answer": 7 },
        { "id": 20, "question": "Evaluate the expression for x = 5: 3x^2 + 2x - 4", "answer": 86 },
        { "id": 21, "question": "Solve for y: 4y + 7 = 2y + 3", "answer": -2 },
        { "id": 22, "question": "Simplify the expression: 3(x + 4) - 2", "answer": "3x + 10" },
        { "id": 23, "question": "Solve the equation: 2y - 3 = 5", "answer": 4 },
        { "id": 24, "question": "Find the value of a: 3(a - 2) = 15", "answer": 7 },
        { "id": 25, "question": "Evaluate the expression for x = -3: (x - 2)^2", "answer": 25 },
        { "id": 26, "question": "Solve for b: 2b + 5 = 13", "answer": 4 },
        { "id": 27, "question": "Simplify the expression: 2x - 4(x - 3)", "answer": "14 - 2x" },
        { "id": 28, "question": "Solve the equation: 3y = 21", "answer": 7 },
        { "id": 29, "question": "Find the value of c: 4c + 3c - 10 = 18", "answer": 4 },
        { "id": 30, "question": "Evaluate the expression for x = 0: -2x^2 + 3x + 5", "answer": 5 }
      ]
  }
  